Jonathan Krause Rare Newspaper and Magazine Collection 1648-1881 E302.1 .J76 E302.1 .J76
Lilly Library
- 17th Century Individuals -- English Civil War, Protectorate, Restoration, Glorious Revolution
  - Richard Cromwell
    - SPEECH OF RICHARD CROMWELL, LORD PROTECTOR, TO PARLIAMENT AFTER DEATH OF HIS FATHER, 1658; Size: Small (Item 927)
  - Charles II
    - CHARLES II NAVAL ACT, 1661; Size: Small (Item 928)
  - James II
    - JAMES II PROCLAMATION ON RELIGIOUS TOLERATION, London Gazette, September 20, 1688 - September 24, 1688; Size: Small (Item 929)
    - JAMES II PROCLAMATION ON IMMINENT INVASION OF WILLIAM, PRINCE OF ORANGE, London Gazette, September 27, 1688 - October 1, 1688; Size: Small (Item 930)
  - William III (Prince of Orange)
    - WILLIAM, PRINCE OF ORANGE ACCEPTS CROWN, London Gazette, December 31-January 3, 1689; Size: Small (Item 931)
    - WILLIAM III PROCLAMATION REQUIRING THE DISCOVERY AND BRINGING IN OF ARMS LATELY EMBEZZLED, London Gazette, April 4, 1689 - April 8, 1689; Size: Small (Item 932)
    - WILLIAM III ON WAR WITH FRANCE, London Gazette, April 25, 1689 - April 29, 1689; Size: Small (Item 933)
    - WILLIAM III AND MARY II PROCLAMATIONS AGAINST CONSPIRATORS AND PAPISTS, London Gazette, June 19, 1690 - June 23, 1690; Size: Small (Item 934)